sprinklecontent.com 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy - Strossle

##  Last updated: April 27, 2018 Privacy Policy 

## **General**

This privacy policy applies to information collected through the Strossle content recommendation and distribution service, i.e., our widgets, video players and sponsored messages installed at our publishing partners’ web pages, (collectively, the “Service”). The Service is offered by Strossle International AB and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Strossle,” or “we”, “us”, “our”).

We take your privacy very seriously and are committed to being transparent with how we use your information. Our privacy policy explains:

  * What information we collect
  * How we use the information we collect
  * Your options to restrict Strossle from accessing information

## What information we collect

**Browser**

We collect information about what type of browser is used (e.g., Chrome, Edge, Firefox, Safari, etc.). We do not collect any additional information about the user agent (e.g., browser version or operating system).

**Location information**

When you use our service, we collect information about what country and county (larger geographical regions) you are browsing from. We do not store detailed geographical locations (e.g., longitude and latitude). We use the location information in order to present recommendations and advertisements that are relevant to a user in a specific region.

**Local storage**

We may store information locally on your device (e.g., using your browsers local storage or cache) in order to understand the usage and with the goal to ultimately improve the user experience. We might track what recommendations are clicked as well as time spent and number of page views on pages and sites. No personal information is processed or stored in association with this analysis.

**Log information**

When you use our service and interact with our recommendations, we collect information about where our service is loaded, what recommendations are displayed and what recommendations are clicked. We use this information in order to optimise recommendations and calculate delivery and payouts for advertisers and publishers. We focus on contextual optimisation and we do not store any personal data of any kind. For legal reasons, we may store IP addresses for up to 60 days if any fraudulent activities occur (see section: How we use the information we collect).

## How we use the information we collect

We use the information we collect to provide, improve and protect our service.

**Billing and payout**

The data we collect when a user interacts with our service, specifically ad recommendations, are analysed in order to deliver the quantity of clicks and/or impressions an advertiser wants to reach. Additionally, we use the collected data for billing and payout purposes to advertisers and publishers.

**Fraud detection**

In order to protect our service and customers (e.g., publishers and advertisers), we use the information we collect to detect and analyse fraudulent activities. We may store the data (including IP address) for up to 60 days before it is deleted.

**Communication and support**

When you contact us, through any of our contact channels (mail, forms, etc.), we keep a record of the communication to help solve any issues you might be facing.

**Better recommendations**

Our service does not rely on personal data but is based on contextual awareness. We use the collected information to improve our contextual understanding and to provide better content recommendation services to our users and better contextual targeting for our advertisers.

**Aggregated data and insights**

The insights we get from aggregated, non-personally identifiable information may be used in marketing communication and with our business partners such as advertisers, publishers and content providers.

## **Children’s information**

Our services are not directed to children under 16. If you learn that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information without consent, please contact us.

## Your options to restrict Strossle from accessing information

**Disable cookies and local storage**

You may set your browser to disable cookies and local storage associated with our service. This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites and services, including this one.

Instructions for how to disable cookies and local storage can be found in your browser’s help section.

**Turn on “Do Not Track” in your browser**

You may activate the “Do Not Track” functionality in your browser. This will prevent our service from to storing recommendations you have clicked, and we will not target any recommendations based on your location information.

Instructions for how to turn on “Do Not Track” can be found in your browser’s help section.

## Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

## Contact information

For questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to reach out to [privacy@strossle.com](mailto:privacy@strossle.com) or call us at +46101991400
